Where do i start?
It's not you.
Well, actually, it is you.
Look, i'm just not--
i'm not attracted
to you any more.
I need space.
You kinda--
You kinda gross me out.
In the beginning, it was different.
In the beginning, you were better.
But then I got to know you
real well, and...
I-- i came to realize...
that you're a fat idiot.
-I got ya. I got ya. I got ya. I got ya.
-Okay. Okay.
- Okay, okay, okay. Let me try it.
- You gotta be straight.
- Okay.
- Straight face.
- Okay, okay.
- All right.
- I want a divorce.
- Why?
It's a physical thing.
- Physical?
- I've been experimenting
with other men lately.
A lot of other men
and women.
I don't know. I mean, Antonio can do
this thing with his tongue...
and William's stamina
is amazing.
And as far as hands go,
well, your father's hands are--
You are no match.
I have no equal.
Get down here.
If the shoe fits
I want you to wear it
and wear it good
Sulkin' about them times
when I was by myseIf
I was always lookin'
for somebody eIse
But as time went on
I had a talk with my mind
Friends like you and you
I gotta leave behind
And i'm sayin' call me a fool
'Cause you only rub it in
- And I'll never see you if i had known
- I'll never see them again
'Cause, well i know the difference
Just stay in my own business
And I'll never, ever
depend on you
Friends and enemies
around me every day
I can't believe
the things they say
Takin' me for granted
Give me no credit at all
I'll just keep bouncin'
like a bouncin' ball
I don't wanna step
on nobody's foot but
You call me a fool
but you only rub it in
And i'll never see you
if i had known
I'll never see that again
'Cause, well i know the difference
Just stay in my own business
And i'll never, ever
depend on you
B-B-B-Brickman's!
B-B-Brickman's Powerboats!
Get it?
Brickman's selIs powerboats.
We make the company mascot
a powerboat. What do you think?
- I like it. Good work, Alan.
- Yes!
- Zachary, you're up.
- All right. I just wanna show you--
- Ladies and gentlemen, Zachary!
- Yes, sir. No--
I haven't taken these to the focus group
yet. i'm still working on that part.
But i just wanted to let you know
these are just preliminary sketches.
Zach.
Ladies and gentlemen, introducing
the new mascot for Hidy Ho Cookies--
Zippy!
What-- What is it?
- Zippy.
- What is Zippy?
- He's a cookie man.
- He's a cookie man?
What is that, uh,
on the ground behind him?
Oh, that's a trail of chocolate chips.
See, wherever Zippy goes...
he leaves this magical trail of
chocolate for all the boys and girIs--
Magical? This-- This looks like poop.
It looks like piles of poop.
- It looks like Zippy's walking around,
ju-- just crapping all over the place.
- Stop.
- It looks like--
- No, no. Those are chocolate chips.
- Emma, what do you think it looks like?
- Excrement.
Zach, let's just say
you're about to take a big bite
of a juicy chocolate chip cookie?
What's the last image you want
floating through your head?
- Excrement?
- Excrement. Right.
Listen, i wanna go out on a limb here.
i'm gonna say maybe we should avoid...
all bowel-related items
with this particular product.
- Just a hunch, you know?
- I'll work up something different.
- All right. Thanks.
- Nick Beam's office.
- Oh, hi, Ann.
- Ooh, aah--
- It's your wife.
Everybody out.
Big business deal.
- Hello.
- Now we're still on for tonight.
You stood me up twice, you know?
It's a done deal. New York
Philharmonic. Last night in town.
I'll be escorting
the sexiest woman in the world.
- What about me?
- We'll bring ya.
Oh, guess what? My sister left
a message on the machine.
And she's coming in
with her fiance next Friday.
- No. Oh, wow.
- Yeah!
I finally get to meet the
mysterious queen of the Peace Corps.
Yes, you do.
Hey, can you pick 'em up?
Yeah, sure. When is it?
A week from today.
I think It'll be around 10:30.
i'm not sure. I'li have to check.
P.B. wants
to see you A.S.A.P.
Sorry, honey, I gotta go. There's
an onslaught of initiaIs coming at me.
- Okay. Tell him hello.
- I will.
- I hate you.
- Me too. Bye.
- Philip.
- Nick.
Oh, oh!
Bungee jumping. Sunday.
Nick!
- No thanks, Phillip.
- P.B.
No thanks, P.B.
- Nick?
- P.B.?
Okay, okay.
Okay, forget it.
- This guy is new.
- Yeah. What do you think?
Uh, i think he likes me.
Niroog, the fertility god.
Boy, i like looking at this.
Handmade in the Paleolithic period.
Had to sacrifice my ldes of March
gold aureus in trade.
Pity. But, uh,
I think worth it.
So, which one of you
wanted to see me?
- Charles McGinty is coming in at 5:00.
- The Charles McGinty?
- ''McGinty Crackers'' Charles McGinty?
- The very same.
- Fantastic.
Anyway, I was supposed to have
dinner with McGinty tonight.
i'd love for you to stand in for me.
Oh, no, uh, s-- Phillip,
I-i promised Ann i-i would--
Nick. Oh, Nick.
You gotta help me out here.
I don't get this lucky
every day.
- Look, if this is about a woman--
- You're a pal. I gotta go.
- it just needs to be--
- Guess who just called?
-Ann's divorce lawyer?
-McGinty's secretary. He's rescheduling.
- All right! Yes!
- Want me to get Ann on the line?
No, i'm gonna try to beat her home.
I wanna surprise her.
This is great, huh?
- The wife again?
- No, actually I just met this
incredible brunette on the elevator.
Well, i'm jealous. What would i
have to do to get flowers all the time?
- You don't get flowers all the time?
- Nope.
That's a crime.
Grab it! Grab it!
That's right. That's right.
Phillip.
Hey, asshole,
get outta the road!
Jump, jump, jump, jump, jump,
jump, jump, jump, jump, jump
I say fight, You're outta the corner
a day late, a dollar short
Friday mornings
most people don't get
You change your life from left to right
You get your wit tracks tight
Must be testing the master
The under hood
the underworld's under man
Never mind being understood
Long as we understand
You can't twist transistor
mixing friends
Soldiers over here don't snitch
They bitch and bit
All hours while
the crowds peepin' in
Welcome to hell, bitch.
Car, keys, wallet. Now!
D'you hear what i said?
Okay. Now you listen,
and you listen good.
This is a gun. Okay? Don't be
fuckin' around with no gun, white boy.
Helen Keller,
i'm talkin' to you.
I know you hear
what the fuck i'm sayin' to you.
Boy, did you pick
the wrong guy on the wrong day.
Oh!
Oh, shit.
Oh, you're trying to lock me--
U-U-Unlock the door.
Stop, motherfucker!
Stop the car! Stop the car!
You're driving on the sidewalk,
man! People got to walk there!
Pull over, man!
White boy, i said pull over!
Yo, man, there's a truck.
I said, yo, man,
there's a truck.
Yo, man, there's a truck
right there. Stop!
What about my wallet?
You wanted to rob me, didn't you?
Yes. I distinctly remember
you wanting to rob me.
Here's my wallet.
You want it?
Here it is. Here. Here.
Right out there.
- What you doin', man? That was money.
- Oh, i'm sorry. I got
something eIse for you.
i'm blind!
I can't see shit.
The honeys dug my eyes.
The honeys loved my eyes.
All right, you win, man. All right?
Is that what you wanna hear? You win.
What the fuck?
No, you ain't one
of them desert slashers, are you?
Cut a person body up and
leave it out in the desert
in little tiny pieces and shit, huh?
Oh, shit!
We are in the fucking desert.
i'm in the car with a psycho,
freaky, Jason hack-killer motherfucker.
Hey, please don't kill me,
freaky Jason.
I said, please don't kill me,
I done fucked around and caught
a ride with the wrong white boy!
- Get out.
- With pleasure.
''Sayo-fuckin'-nara,'' pal.
I can't feel my ass.
My ass just fell asleep.
I didn't even know
an ass could fall asleep!
It's all tingly and shit!
Come on, man.
You can't leave me out here.
Yo, man! You can't
just leave me out here.
Okay, i'll make
a deal with you.
You drive me home, i'll forget
about this whole kidnapping shit.
Oh, come on.
Hello. You tried to rob me.
You had a gun to my head.
Look, i told you
the gun wasn't loaded.
You got yourseIf into this.
You know what you are? You're
a bad person. You're an armed robber.
Don't expect me
to feel sorry for you.
Excuse me.
Is there a problem here?
- Yes.
- Is this man botherin' you?
- Yes, he is.
- Oh, so you're just gonna come
right at the brother.
Why don't you ask
if he's bothering me?
Lady, for all you know,
I could be DenzeI washington.
Take a good look.
He could be some
celebrity stalker.
i'm gonna have to ask you
to pay for this coffee now...
'cause I've seen these things
escalate before.
No problem. My wallet.
Wow! Looks like the celebrity stalker
don't have a wallet.
Oh, well, thank you.
I will get your change, sir.
What? You want me to thank you?
So i owe you a buck.
How was you goin' to get gas? You don't
have no money, no credit cards.
No I.D.
Shit, man.
Okay. All right.
You give me money for gas
and i'll take you back.
I'm cool. i'm--
i'm straight.
As a matter of fact, i-- you know,
i like it out here in the desert.
You know, you get
all sweaty and shit.
Just bubbling off your ass.
Just-- What?
I just remembered.
I have a spare credit card
in the side compartment.
Uh-huh, right here!
What's up?
What's up, white boy?
W-W-What's up, huh?
Come on, come on.
What ya got?
Huh? Look at you. You done
fucked around and got dropped.
Get the fuck outta here.
- What?
- You hit like a ole girl, man.
Get the fuck on out of here, man.
Go about your business.
Motherf--
What the hell is this,
your merry-go-round move?
Yo, i understand.
Aha!
Thank you.
Hey. Oh, shit.
I didn't know it was expired.
I never use it.
So why are you out here?
- What do you care?
- i'm curious.
i'm a student
of human nature.
You're a freak
That's all right.
I forgive you.
It's clear you have
woman problems.
You're way off base.
- i'm off base?
- Yeah. Way off base.
- She mess around on you?
- Look.
Even if i wanted to talk about it--
which I don't-- it wouldn't be with you.
You give her some nastiness? i know you
gave her some serious nastiness.
- Just forget it.
- What about him? Did you fuck him up?
Did you whoop his ass? I bet you hit
that motherfucker with a bat, didn't ya?
Kling! Pow! Fucked his ass up,
didn't ya?
No, wait a minute. You capped him. You
capped that motherfucker, didn't you?
That's why you out here
in the desert, ain't ya?
Look. i didn't shoot him. I didn't say
anything to my wife. I just left.
- What do you mean, you just left?
- Just left. I--
I saw them doing you know...
and i walked away.
What a pussy.
No wonder your woman
is sneaking behind your back, man.
Know what your problem is? You don't
have the respect of your woman, man.
That's what it is.
Me, I got all that.
I go home, my dinner's
on the table.
Bam! I don't wanna
hear shit, woman.
- And if i want lovin'-- if i'm
in the mood-- i get that too.
- You're so full of shit.
What would you have done?
Man, i would have went back
to that house and i'd have pulled
a Terminator on the front door.
Boom, boom, boom! Who the fuck do you
think you're playin' with, woman?
Who do you think i am, some fruity pie?
I ain't no fruity pie.
i'm-- i'm Nick Beam.
That's what i told her.
i'm Nick Beam.
And Nick Beam ain't puttin' up
with that bullshit.
She'd have been crying, you know ? ''Oh,
Nick, oh, Nick, please take me back.
Please, please, Nick.
it was only one time.''
i'm gonna ''one time'' your ass.
Nick Beam is the master of his fate...
the ruler of his destiny.
So if you wanna cry
on somebody's shoulder,
why don't you cry on Superdick?
As for Nick Beam,
i'm fit, lit...
and i damn sure
ain't takin' no shit.
So you can get the fuck out.
That's what i woulda
told the bitch.
That's what i
- What the--
- Hey, hold it. Hold it.
Break it up. Break it up.
What's goin' on here?
Should i pay cash, or do you
wanna use your credit card?
Ah, fu-- Oh-- Ah--
Oh, shit.
- Put the money in the bag.
Put the money in the fuckin' bag!
- Okay.
- Shit.
- let's go! Put the money
in the fuckin' bag.
Shit.
You weren't gonna leave
without me, were you?
- What do you think you're doing?
- There's a special they got goin' on.
You get a free stack of cash
with every fill-up. Some luck, huh?
How stupid can you be?
- We better get out of here.
- You take that money back.
- i'm serious, man. We better get goin'.
- We'll get goin' as soon you
bring back that money.
- i'm not bullshittin'! Move out!
- i'm not going anywhere
until you return--
Here we go.
- Why? Why? Why?
- I didn't have any money, man.
- Oh, you had money.
- No. No. That five dollars
i gave the waitress was it.
- What the--
- Oh, great. Buford's come to kill us.
- Persistent hillbilly motherfucker.
- He has every right to be.
You robbed him at gunpoint.
You dick!
Hey, hey, you're the one who threw
the wallet out the fuckin' window.
Smart.
Great!
Oh, shit.
- All right, man. What you doin'?
- Come on, asshole.
Well, would you look
at these crazy sons a bitches?
Oh, shit. We gonna die.
Pull off the fuckin' road.
Man, would you pull
off the fuckin' road!
Oh, shit!
- Oh, shit!
- Oh, shit.
Hey, Earl.
Oh, sh--
I'm alive! You alive!
How'd you know that hillbilly
was gonna turn first?
You did know he was gonna
turn first, didn't ya?
You know what?
it don't even matter.
I'm alive!
You alive, man!
- Get out!
- What?
What are you even thinking when
you do something like that?
- You think you're never
gonna get caught?
- We didn't get caught.
That's not the point.
It's beetleheaded.
It's-- It's only a matter of time
before you do get caught.
- What is beetleheaded?
- It's a synonym for ''stupid.''
Oh. Well, here's a synonym
for ''procreation.'' Fuck you!
It's easy for you to point the finger
when you're sittin' on your rich ass
in a big fuckin' house.
- I'm not rich.
- Oh, yeah.
- How big's your TV?
- What?
- I say, how big's your TV?
- Fifty-inch.
- Get in the car.
- Oh, please. let's not
make this a social issue.
The point is that even
if you wanted to rob a place,
there are smarter ways to do it.
- Enlighten me.
- A mask. Wear a mask.
You see, the police
have this thing called a ''lineup...''
and if someone recognizes you,
you go to jail!
Oh, how about this for a novel idea?
Case the place first.
Find out if there's a security camera
or a hidden alarm.
Then again, why even rob
a convenience store?
How much money could you possibly get?
Two, three hundred dollars?
Then what? You're set
for two days! Wow!
- What do you know, lanky?
- i know you go for the big score.
One robbery, you're set.
News flash, big slim.
People with big money,
they protect it.
So you do a little research.
Take Quality Design Group where i work.
My boss keeps a ton of cash
in his vauit.
At night, there's only two guards
and a personal security system.
Now, in this case,
i happen to even know the code.
But even if l didn't, l--
What?
I got a booger in my nose?
Diversify.
You can't trust banks, Nick.
The entire system
could crumble at any second.
That bastard's so heavily leveraged,
it would wipe him out.
Wait a minute.
Am i hearing you right?
Mr ''High and Mighty''
is gonna rob his boss?
You hear that,
gila monsters?
Old Nick Beam here
is gonna rob his boss!
I say, do you hear that,
gila monsters?
You know what, Nick? Your wife really
messed your head up bad, man.
You're serious?
- How much he got?
- Only the bulk of his personal assets.
- Six, seven hundred thousand.
- You what?
- Hey, you gonna need some help.
- Oh, no, this has nothing
to do with you.
Hey, I was present at the time
of creative inspiration...
which entitles me
to partial ownership...
in this
criminalistic endeavour.
- Get out.
- Maybe i'll just call Quality
Design Group when we get back.
I want haIf.
We're gonna bury
this asshole.
Sure, you're right.
If you ever plan
To motor West
Travel my way
Take the highway
That's the best
Come on
Get your kicks
On Route Sixty--
Six
Well, it winds from Chicago
To L.A.
More than 2,000 miles
- Highway shooters?
- One black, one white. You tell me?
You were there,
and they got away?
They were driving
a 1996 Yukon.
- Licence?
- You know, if i had a licence number,
Bart, i wouldn't be standing here...
- eating large quantities
of shit, now, would i?
- No, sir.
Monitor calls on both sides
of the border. Fax that photo
to every precinct on the planet.
There's so much as a sneeze
out there i wanna feel the mist.
I hear a voice
- Give me all your money and a Yoo Hoo.
- The money's all locked up.
That'll be 79 cents, please.
I said
Come on, little prisoner
I got something to say
Something stinks, man.
You sure you ain't got
a gas leak?
- It's my shoes.
- Your shoes?
You ever heard of Dr Scholl's?
I spilled some gas on my shoes
at the gas station.
You know,
the one you robbed.
- Oh, so you got a camcorder up in here.
- What are you doing?
i'm just
checkin' it out, man.
- Pu-- Pu-- Put it down.
- I ain't gonna break it, man.
Just let me check it out.
Just let me see.
Yo, this is your wife?
Man, i see why
you were upset.
Not bad, Nick.
I mean, you know,
for a cheatin' bitch.
Look, don't you call her that.
You-- You don't know her.
Don't call her that.
Okay. No disrespect. Okay?
What should l call her?
Monogamously challenged?
- God.
- I was just fuckin' with you, man.
You know, this is an all right camera
for a regular eight.
- It's the best on the market.
- Let me explain something to you, Nick.
If you ain't got digital,
you ain't got shit.
This has only got
one C.C.D. chip.
Broadcast has three, Nick.
Don't look at me like that.
What, are you surprised i know shit?
The guy that sold me that camera
just set up our computer network.
- Windows NT?
- No. Just Windows.
- Man, get out of here with that shit.
- Look, here's a nutty idea.
If you actually know something about
this stuff, why not use that knowledge
and get a job?
Take a good look at me.
- i'm not exactly the corporate colour.
- That's ridiculous.
- If you wanted a job,
you could have one.
- There's a spider on your head.
- What?
Look, i am sorry.
i am not up on all this...
jive-talkin', homeboy lingo.
What's that supposed to mean,
there's a spider on your head?
it means: There's a spider on
your motherfuckin' head, man.
Well, get it off!
Get it off, get it off!
- I ain't touchin' that shit.
- Get it off!
Get it off, get it off,
get if off, get if off!
- Get it off!
- Yo, that's a big fuckin' spider, man.
Oh, shit!
Nick, it's just a spider.
i'm a scat man
No, no.
Now don't go crazy.
- Yeah, you go, boy.
- i'm a scat man
Hold on, let me focus.
Let me focus on this shit.
i'm a scat man
Oh, shit.
You got the hot foot!
Yo, Nick!
Get on the good foot.
Get on the good--
Aw, got it!
i'm a scat man
I gotta make a call.
You pump.
- Give me the gun.
- What?
Give me the gun.
Man, I wasn't gonna
rob the place, man.
Then you won't need this.
You must be really fast.
Twenty dollars on pump number 15
and a sour fruity twist.
- You a cop?
- No.
You bastards have tried this
too many times!
- Oh, listen--
- Shut up!
- I wasn't gonna--
- Shut up.
Emmitt County Sheriff's Station.
Hello. Hello.
- Uh--
- Yes, may i help you?
That show, Cops...
I love it.
Have you ever had
a really bad day?
i'm havin' one right now.
Now, look, baby,
I told you i'd be home later.
Now, this guy say he got a job
for me, okay, payin' big money.
Okay, now, please, don't argue with me.
Not-Not now. All right?
I'll see you later. Okay.
Oh, oh. Oh.
Now all i want's $20 on pump number 15
and a sour fruity twist.
- Is that too much to ask?
- No, sir.
- Do you mind if i take your gun?
Would you please rip the phone cord
out of the wall?
- What?
- Would you rip the phone cord
out of the wall, please?
Thank you. This is for the phone and for
the gun and for the sour fruity twist.
And $20 on pump number 15. Go on.
- Thank you for your patience.
- Yes, sir.
Le-- Let me get this straight.
It's all right for you to rob a place,
but it ain't all right for me?
I didn't rob him.
Well, you got a funny way
of not robbin' a motherfucker.
Nick, let's get out of here,
man, before he calls the cops.
- He's not gonna call the cops.
- How do you know?
I had him rip the phone cord
out of the wall.
Oh, shoot.
That's pretty good.
And you got his gun?
Not bad, Nicholas.
Not bad.
Charlie, this shit's depressing the shit
out of me. It's makin' me sad.
What? Oh, come on, man.
This shit is the shit.
- This is the shit.
It's supposed to make you sad.
- It's grim.
Oh, man, come on.
This is the shit.
This shit is the shit.
This is the hellified love music.
- i'm in bad shape over here.
- Ah, man, you know, maybe i can...
tune you in to a nice A.M. station
and get you some Donny Osmond.
- Charlie, what's this? Slow down.
- Get the fuck out of here.
Pull over and
turn the headlights off.
Yo, man, you could've
gotten me a piece of licorice.
- It's sour.
- So.
Still could've gotten me a piece.
- I didn't think of it.
- Oh, you didn't think of it.
Just seIfish, man.
Guess that's the world.
- You know? You just-- You just seIfish.
- Here.
Damn.
I swear, white people must got
totally different taste buds, man.
That's a very
racist thing to say.
Oh, yeah? Good.
What the f--
- Oh, shit!
- Whoa, they're rammin' us.
Thanks for the late-breakin' news.
Step on the gas, Nick!
I hate new cars.
Whoa!
Look at his face, man.
Look, man!
Our turf, baby.
They don't look like cops.
Definitely not cops.
Get out of the car.
- There you go.
- All right, motherfuckers,
back the fuck off!
Oh, shit. It's cool.
Oh, yeah, i'm cool.
We cool.
I was just fuckin'
with y'all, man.
Hey, what's up?
Y'all-Y'all live around here?
Bring your ass
around the front of the car.
Come on, baby. Come on, baby.
There you go. There you go.
- All right. Okay. Oh, shit.
- Uh-huh. Watch your feet.
- Uh-huh.
Come on, rubber legs. let's go.
Watch where you're walkin'.
Watch-- Watch your feet.
There you go, baby.
Perhaps you two haven't heard
that my partner and i here...
own the rights to all violent crime
on this particular stretch of highway.
And we don't take kindly to any
unauthorized criminal activities.
You don't understand.
We were--
- Oh, shit.
- That's my car.
- Can i have your attention, please?
- Yeah.
I bet you used to sell more
Girl Scout cookies than any other member
of the whole troop, didn't ya?
What were you calling yourseIf back
then? Yolanda, you little bitch?
Cynthia? Susan? What was it?
I can't remember.
- Hey, guys, i will be gentle.
Don't even worry about it.
- Huh?
Now-- Now, don't even worry.
Uh-huh.
I have these.
Oh, now that's not
gonna be enough.
Where'd you put your booty?
Now I've done it. I finally found
someone i like less than you.
Shit. That's
a fancy case, friend.
You know, when a sweet-mouthed girl
like you has a fancy case like this...
a man gets to thinkin'
where's the wallet?
That's it.
We're dead, man.
i'm gonna need
that wallet, Alice.
Where's that big, fat wallet?
Give it to me.
Give me your fuckin' wallet,
you little bitch.
- You know what?
- Nick, Nick, what you doin'?
i'm sure you're
a really scary guy.
i'm sure that, normally, people just
quiver at the very sound of your voice.
But, you see, i, i can't
see that right now.
I-i-i just see a weak,
desperate little man...
that probably grew up
torturing little animaIs.
Some puny, little uncoordinated...
can't-make-the-football-team-
so-I'll-pick-on-third-graders-
and-steal-their-lunch-money...
punk, jerk-off bully...
that one day wakes up
and realizes he's nothing.
Just a sad, pathetic, useless,
illiterate piece of inbred shit.
I just want you to know,
I totally disagree.
- Time to die.
- That just makes you my best friend.
All right,
drop the fuckin' gun.
Drop the fuckin' gun!
Give me this, motherfucker.
Now back the fuck up before
I kick you in your bitch-ass chin.
Back the fuck up!
I said, back the fuck up!
Didn't I say, back the fuck up?
Everybody, back the fuck up.
Oh!
Shit.
- You shot me.
- i'm sorry, Nick.
- Put down the gun.
- Shut up.
- You shot me.
- I said, i'm sorry, man.
I-i-i didn't mean it.
The gun just went off.
You know, i have that
same trouble in bed.
Well, rarely. Every once
in a great while.
- Put down that gun, you idiot.
- Would you shut up? i'm shot here.
You shut the fuck up.
Who the hell do you think you are?
- You shut the fuck up!
You shut the fuck up!
- Huh? Look at yourseIf, you candy-ass--
- Man, you shut the fuck up.
- You shut the fuck up.
- Shut up!
- Put down the gun!
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Put that fucking gun down
before you take a fucking toe hit.
- You shut the fuck up!
- I don't give a shit!
- Shut the fuck up!
- Candy-ass motherfucker!
- Shut the fuck up, man!
- Shut the fuck up!
- Hey, hey, hey!
Hey! Everybody,
shut the fuck up!
Now, everybody,
Especially you.
Shut the fuck up.
You like Girl Scout cookies?
Come here. Come here.
You want cookie?
Here's a cookie.
Now back the fuck up like i done
told you two dumb-ass mother--
Back up, back up.
Get in the car, Nick!
Look at you now.
That's good.
Bye, cowboys!
Nick, why the hell you start up
with that guy, man?
- You shot me.
- i'm sorry.
You don't say you're sorry
when you shoot someone.
You say you're sorry when
you step on someone's toe...
or you accidentally
break their glasses...
or you, you fart
while they're eating.
You-- You don't say you're sorry
when you shoot someone!
Shit.
Oh, my God. It's going numb.
It's going numb. It's going numb.
What?
Shit.
Oh, my God!
Nick, that's the most
hideous thing i ever seen.
Hey, yo, man, you know,
maybe if you wrap your arm in ice...
they can reattach it.
That's funny, man.
- That's a baby gash.
- Shut up.
- But it's a baby gash.
- It could've been a lot worse.
It could've been a lot worse!
- it could've been,
but it wasn't. i'm gonna--
- What are you thinking, shooting?
Look, just calm down,
all right?
You're gonna upset your wound.
Yeah. Do you folks
want a lift somewhere?
- Where you from?
- London.
- Me too!
- Really?
- Yeah!
- That's terrific.
Hop in me car. let's go then.
Come on. Jump in. let's go.
- Oh, this is great.
- Hey, would you scoot over a smidgen?
Sorry about that.
Cheers, mate.
- Nick Beam.
- Where we headed?
L.A.
City of AngeIs.
So where you plan
on stayin' tonight?
- I'll just sleep in the car.
- Yeah, right.
You can stay at my place,
brother.
Thanks.
Well, just for the night.
What? Did you think
I was asking you to move in?
- No, I was just sayin'--
- Please, Mr Beam.
- Stay with me forever.
- Just shut up.
- Mr Beam.
- Shut up.
- Mr Beam, Mr Beam, Mr Beam.
- You know how to shut up?
- Mr Beam.
- Is it in your vocabulary?
- Stay with me forever, Mr Beam.
- Is it possible? Do you ever shut up?
Will you stay with me
forever, Mr Beam?
Look here.
When you meet my wife...
she don't know nothin'
about my sideline gig.
- You mean she doesn't know
you're a thief?
- Hey, i'm not a thief, okay?
I just dabble
in future used goods.
- Well, what does she think
you do all day?
- Look for work, man.
Maybe if you did look for work,
you wouldn't have to steal.
Don't judge me.
You stepped on my shoe.
See, I don't usually
get in this late.
Baby, am i glad
to see you.
No, no, no. No, talk to me.
Explain this to me now.
I got mugged.
- Okay, i didn't get mugged.
- I got--
- I got mugged. He got beat up.
- Thank--
Remember how I was tellin' you
i  had a job interview?
Baby, that's him.
He right there.
That's the player
right there.
My name's Nick. Nick Beam.
Nice to meet you.
When are you gonna stop
gettin' into trouble, Terrance?
- Terrance?
- ''T.''
Okay? My friends call me ''T.''
You can kiss my ass. Boo!
- Okay, Terrance.
- Oh, Mama.
Please go on
back to bed, Mama.
What kind of man stays out
till 2:30 in the morning...
then comes back lookin'
like a bruised turd?
- Mama, i ain't--
- Don't you talk back.
Don't talk back
to your mother.
W-- What-- What'd i do?
You got that slap
'cause you with him.
- And i know you're part of
whatever badness he's into.
- Mama, enough.
You got some explainin'
to do in the morning, Mr Gentleman.
Now you think on that.
Why do you keep on
smackin' me, Mama?
Okay.
- Shh.
- No, go ahead. Go ahead.
- Okay.
- Oh.
Okay, now you come here.
Come here.
Mama didn't have to
smack me three times.
- We gotta move out of here.
- i know.
- I know.
- I heard gunshots.
Hey, there, boy. Hey, what
you doing up this late, pal?
Huh? What's up?
What are you doing up this late?
Oh, honey, we woke you.
Now look, don't worry.
Give Daddy a kiss. Come on.
Don't worry. I ain't gonna let nothin'
happen to y'all. You know that, right?
- What happened to your face?
- No, i'm cool, little man.
Hey, you do your homework?
- Yes, sir.
- I said, did you do your homework?
- Hmm? Hmm?
- Y-- Yes, sir.
- What about you, little miss?
Did you do all your homework?
- I don't have any homework.
You don't have no homework? All right,
time to go back to bed. Let's go.
Hut-two-three-four
Make a right at the right door
Make your choice 'cause you got
to grow up to be successful
- I hope this isn't
an inconvenience for you.
- Not at all.
You seem like a nice man. Terrance
can use a few of those in his life.
- Good night.
Thanks.
Hey.
You know, i never noticed before,
but you got really nice eyes.
- Shut up!
- But you do.
Let's get this over with.
I can't believe it. i'm committing
armed robbery for two flashlights.
Hey, don't worry about it.
Let's go.
Freeze, motherfucker!
You move your ass so much
as an inch, I'll blow it off!
- You hear me, motherfucker?
- Hey.
- You hear me? What?
- Why you acting so mean?
- Hey, look, man. Now ain't
the fuckin' time, all right?
- You say scary shit, it scares 'em.
- Yeah, but you have a gun.
Plus, what you're doing
is a stereotypical robber thing.
I mean, it's a lot scarier
if someone with a gun is calm
and cool and collected, man.
- That's bullshit, man. Don't--
- Here.
Excuse me, sir. Come here.
Come here. Come here.
Now, look, Henry...
we're gonna take
some things outta here...
and you're just gonna
stand there.
- You got a problem with that?
- No.
Good.
Now, honestly, which one
did you think was scarier?
- Honestly?
- Mm-hmm.
He was scarier.
Really? You didn't find
what he did contrived?
- No. it was scary.
- Well, what part?
Well, the, uh, ''Freeze, motherfucker''
part was scary.
And then he led me to believe
that if i moved my ass...
it, it might be blown off.
- You were scary too.
- Oh, come on. You're just saying that.
You don't have to lie.
No, i'm not. I thought
you were very scary.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Well, thank you, Henry.
- Yo, check it out.
They're flashlights
with A.M./F.M. radio on it.
They all that. You can listen to
your music while the light's on, boy.
All right, all right!
Come on. Come on.
Freeze, sucker-bitch!
That was much better.
Thank you, Henry.
See ya later now.
What the hell is
''sucker-bitch''?
I wanna live in the jungle
Where you don't got
to wear no clothes
And they got no boutiques
Nothin' chic
In the jungle
they don't have no disco
Yo, yo, Rig!
Hey, yo, Rig!
Yeah, come on over here
and meet Ginger and Mary Ann.
Ow! God!
Charlie, we gotta go!
Go, go, go, go, go, go
- Break, break
- Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go
- Hey, Nick, what floor is it on?
- Fifteenth.
- What-- What-- What fifteenth?
- Come on.
Why can't we just
use the elevator?
- 'Cause there's a guard
that patroIs the building.
- This is bullshit!
Come on, man. It's Saturday night.
They're not gonna be there anyway.
Look, i know we're gonna go
back Monday and we're gonna get him.
I just wanna check it out.
Take a left here, will you?
You seriously busted up my party.
You know that.
Those girIs were attracted
to you. I mean, Christ's sake,
they're only human.
-You're a handsome man. We will go back.
-I'll hold you to that.
- Okay.
- Mm-hmm. What's the matter with you?
- You sharp.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Beat you.
- I carried the damn bag.
- I still beat you.
Beat me at what?
Climbing steps?
Guess we'll call you
the ''Step King.''
Oh, shit.
No problem.
i know the code.
- What?
- Come on. Come on.
Shit! That asshole
must've changed the code.
Step aside. Let me take a look.
Let me take a look.
Okay, let me look.
Mm-hmm.
- What are you gonna do?
- You got 12 possible stations here.
You're only using seven.
i'm gonna make the other five stations
active, run a test mode...
and force the system
into rotation.
What does that mean?
We got five minutes.
Here. Put on your mask.
Is that mask sweaty? I think
that's the one i hid behind my balls.
All right.
- Yeah, all right.
- All right, all right.
Ooh, yeah. let's go.
We got three minutes. let's go.
- Lookin' good.
- Yeah.
Put the money in there.
let's go. All right. let's go.
Here we go. Money. Money.
Let's go. Mask, mask.
Let's go, baby.
Let's go, baby. let's go!
What the hell are you doin'?
Nick?
Okay, that's real clever, Nick.
let's go.
Come on, man.
This is very nice.
It's very nice. It's very nice.
Oh. I don't think I've ever seen
a more beautiful piece of shit.
Nick. Nick!
Very nice. Very nice.
Very nice.
Yeah!
That's great. That's great.
You done cut the dick off a statue.
How's it feel, Phillip?
You had it all, but it wasn't enough
for you. You had to mess with me.
Nobody messes with Nick Beam.
I feel lucky
I just feel that way
i'm on a bus to Atlantic City
Later on today
- Your face, man. You showed your face.
- it doesn't matter.
it does matter. They catch you,
they catch me. it damn well matters!
- i'm a winner
- Hey, man, look at me.
Look at me, man.
i'm not goin' down for this shit.
And now i know
Why I've been sent
Little rump shaker
She can really shake and bake
She's got skills
- Watch her slippin' and a slidin'
- Here, man!
- Makin' booty left to right
- Here!
She's got skills
Hmm. The alarm
must've been set.
Addressing the groove
I see you're drinkin' again
You're smokin' smack inside your
cigarettes and lookin' pale and thin
It's a shame
It's a pity in New York City
Well
Well, well, well
well, well
Something has changed
The way these people think
Hey there, lonely girl
Lonely girl
Let me make your
broken heart like new
- Oh, shit.
- Hey there, lonely--
White people.
Our dates.
Ohh, shit.
Oh-ho-ho.
Look at this, man!
Mama-say, mama-sa, makusa!
Oh, smack me two times!
Calm down.
My son is going
to the best schooIs.
My daughter, she ain't even
gonna know what a food stamp is.
My wife,
we goin' out all the time.
All the time!
- What's wrong with you, man?
- Nothing.
You sweatin' that bullshit, ain't you?
You sweatin' that bullshit.
You did what you had to do
to that guy, man. Don't worry about it.
All right? Put that shit
behind you, man. Where you goin'?
Where you goin'?
i'm just gonna--
i'm just gonna take a walk.
All right.
Well, hurry back.
I got willpower,
but I don't know how much.
You know what i'm sayin'?
Yeah.
There is somethin'
On your mind
By the way
you look at me
There is somethin'
On your mind, honey
Did you ever do somethin' that you
thought would make you feel great?
In a weird way,
you almost feel worse.
Revenge, huh?
Some things hurt no matter what.
That must be a fact
of life.
- And what you're thinkin'
- Hi!
Hi! Nick.
I can't believe it.
What are you doin' here?
- Danielle.
- Oops.
I don't know
what i'm doin' here.
- What are you doin' here?
- Well, Sheila, my best friend--
Well, she used to be my best friend.
I guess, technically,
Marcy would be my best friend.
I mean, they both think they're my
best friend, which is okay by me.
But once i did have this nightmare
where Sheila and Marcy are sitting...
right next to each other, and this
Eskimo guy comes over and says, ''Pick.''
I thought I was gonna die. I mean,
an Eskimo guy. What is that all about?
Anyway, Sheila, she's visiting
and she's staying here.
And so i thought i'd take her
to a party and show her a good time.
And she meets this guy and goes home
with him instead. And, oh, well.
You really look good.
You look--
You look good too.
- Thank you.
- Do you want a drink?
Uh-huh. Yeah. Sure.
You know, i'm such a klutz. I spilled
beer all over my dress earlier.
And, well, i think it's stained.
Did it stain, Nick?
I have Sheila's room key.
You wanna come up?
- Let's get hot
- Oh, yes, it's ladies' night
And the vibes is right
Oh, yes, it's ladies' night
Oh, what a night
It's ladies' night
and the feeling's right
Oh, yes, it's ladies' night
Oh, what a night
Nick, Nick,
use your key, man.
All right.
All right, Nick. Damn!
- Hey, Nick, why couldn't
you just use your key?
- Turn your bed down?
Stay.
The lady is lookin' good
- Just like the lady should
I've been thinking about this
for so long. I want you so bad.
I just wanted to
make her happy.
This is gonna be a night
that you won't forget.
I try to forget,
but i can't.
- Give it to me, Nick.
- Give. That's all i did was give.
Nick? Nick, you're really putting
a damper on the mood here.
i'm sorry.
I don't know.
Danielle, I can't.
I just can't.
I just wanna make you mine
We'll be together
till the end of time
Hey, Kareem. Are you aware
that Charlie and i...
had intended to come up here
and cap your punk ass?
And your girIfriend Nick.
But, shit, you two muffins did such an
outstanding job with this financing...
I mean, who could think about killing
at a time like this?
Thanks. Your approval
means a lot.
- Did i tell you to speak?
Did i tell you to speak?
- Charlie, no.
That's gonna be too loud.
Too loud.
- Hello? Hello?
- Hi.
Oh, my God!
Nick, is that you? Are you okay?
- i'm fine.
- Oh, thank God!
I didn't know if, if you--
I thought that--
You're not hurt?
- No.
- Oh, thank God! Where are you?
Look, Ann, let's not make this harder
than it has to be. I saw you.
- What?
- I saw you. I know.
Saw me what?
What are you talking about?
Come on. Do you have to do this?
You and Phillip.
- What about him?
- You're denying it. She's denying it.
I don't believe this.
Friday afternoon. Remember?
Well, guess what.
I came home early. I saw you, Ann.
- I was there.
- Oh. Oh, no.
Yeah. Oh, no.
Nick, I was still
at work Friday afternoon.
At work? Well, then your-your clone
was at home screwing my boss.
Nick, it was my sister.
Remember, i told you...
she was coming next Friday
with her fiance?
Well, i made a mistake. It was this
Friday. They called from the airport.
I told them about
the key in the planter.
I called you, but you'd
already left the office.
So i left you a message
on the machine at home.
What about-- What about the cuff links?
Phillip's cuff links
were on the sink, Ann.
Honey, they've been in the dresser
since the Christmas party.
I left them on the counter so you'd
finally remember to bring them to him.
So you're not having
an affair?
- No, you dick!
- You still love me?
More than anything in the world.
You-- You wouldn't believe
what I've been through.
You're gonna laugh,
but i actually-- Shit.
- What's the matter? What's wrong?
- Shit!
- What's the matter? What?
Shit! Shit!
Shit, shit, shit, shit,
shit, shit, shit...
shit, shit, shit, shit,
shit, shit.
Going down.
- Don't touch it.
- Oh, man.
Oh, man.
I think i can open the door
and catch the sheet.
- Don't touch the sheet, please. Don't--
- No, no, no.
- No, don't move. Don't move.
- Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
I done moved the hand.
I really don't think
you should be moving right now.
I-i think you're moving.
- Call the paramedics. Listen to me.
- All right.
Get them here
as fast as you can!
Have them meet me
with a gurney.
- Wait. Let me practise.
- Let you practise?
i'm hangin' on
a fuckin' ledge, man.
- I don't wanna die like this, Nick.
- All right.
I wasn't tryin'
to stick you up, man!
First, i'm gonna say ''one.''
Then i'm gonna say ''two.''
Then i'm gonna say ''three.''
- And then i'm gonna do it.
- I can't hear you.
- i'm gonna start with one
and count to three!
- Okay.
Ready?
One.
- Right.
- Two.
I can't hear you!
You gotta be louder, Nick!
- I said, ''two''!
- Are you on ''two'' already?
- I'll start again!
- Start from ''one''!
- One..
- Right.
- Two.
- I got you.
- Three!
- Nick!
- I got it! I got it! Got it!
Well, you go, boy!
You my--
The elevator!
The money!
Remind me to kick
your ass later.
Oh! We're rich, man!
- We are in the bigs.
- Charlie. Charlie, smell that.
Oh, yes! You, too,
can be a millionaire!
Hookers!
Charlie, Charlie, Charlie,
Charlie, smell this.
More hookers!
- Hookers!
- We hit the mother lode, man!
- What the fuck is that?
- What the fuck--
- Okay. What now?
- I don't know.
What do you mean, you don't know?
I thought you said you had a plan.
- That was my plan: to ram them.
- Ram them.
Speed up!
- Shoot the mother-- Shoot him!
- I got him! I got him!
- Shoot 'em!
- Geez!
You know, i'm tired of this shit.
Let's go!
Charlie!
Look out, Charlie!
I'm actually grabbing a gun
and going after bad guys.
You the man.
All right.
- You see 'em?
- No.
I'll, uh--
I'll let you know.
Please do.
Nick.
What?
- You checkin' this shit out?
- Hey, Nick.
I like you like this.
You and your prom date
both having weapons.
That way I don't have to kill
an unarmed couple. It's not my style.
Put down the bag.
- Paul Bunyan, come and take the bag.
- Nick, let me--
- You're an idiot! Shut up!
- Shoot this mother--
- No, you're a fuckin' idiot!
Who are you? Crime dog now?
Are you aware that there's only
two kind of people on the whole planet?
There are killers,
and then there's everybody eIse.
i'm a killer, Nick. Yes, yes, yes, yes.
What are you, Nick?
i'm married.
Oh, you son of a--
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, shit!
What are you,
fuckin' out of your mind?
- Fuck!
- What, are you crazy?
Huh? Who's in control now?
Hand over the bag...
or eIse my man Nick Beam here
gonna put one in your ass.
Ain't that right, Nick?
- I'll roll over.
- Okay, i see it. I see it.
Let me try to get around
and get you.
No, it's not--
- No, they're in the alley.
- Charlie, it's the police.
- Oh, yes!
- Thank God you're here.
- Thank God you're here, man.
- Oh, this nightmare's over.
- What the fuck are you doin'?
- Put the gun down!
Put that gun down,
you stupid pig!
- Wait! Come on!
- Come on, man!
It's them.
Well, some folks in Arizona are
gonna be mighty happy to see you boys.
Wait, wait, wait! Officer! Officer!
Officer, two other guys--
''i'm married.'' Ka-blam!
You're too much.
- Is the money all there?
- Looks like it.
Great. We have just enough time
to get it back.
Excuse me?
We have to bring the money back.
No, no.
Maybe you're a little bit confused
about the purpose of a robbery.
Oh, T., i didn't tell you. When we
were at the hotel, i called my wife.
Everything's all right.
You see, it wasn't her.
She wasn't even there.
Isn't that great?
it was her sister
and her sister's fiance.
I don't give a damn if it was
her Uncle Fester and Gumby.
You ain't takin'
this money anywhere, man.
I don't wanna
hear all that.
- Let go. Let go.
- Gimme the bag. You let go.
- Let go of the bag. You let--
- It's not your money.
- It's not your money!
- It's not yours. It's haIf mine.
- Let go!
- You let go!
Let go!
Get back here!
- You okay?
- Yeah, i'm okay.
- And you?
- I'll live.
Can't let you take
the money, Nick.
T., my life is in that bag.
Nick, even if you wanted
to take the money back, you can't.
- Your face is on the video, man.
- They only review the tapes
if something's missing.
I can go into work early
and bring it back. No one'li know.
T.
I can get my life back.
You forget one thing, Nick.
I get my life back too.
Money don't make
my world go 'round
i'm reaching out
for the higher ground
To a warm and peaceful place
I can rest my weary face
Life's answers we try to find
Oh, we try to find
Yes, we try to find
Battling inside our minds
Where do i go from here
Will all my friends be there
'Cause we're living
we're living
In a crazy maze
And we're fighting
we're fighting
To rise above the haze
Lights at the end
of the tunnel
Sometimes the journey's long
There are many theories
Who's right and who's wrong
Pressure's on
i have to choose
I've got nothing to lose
I close my eyes
i take a chance
I-i, i now dance
a different dance
What's the key
to a happy life
Tell me now, now, now
Heaithy mind
and lots of spice
Running barefoot
through the trees
- Oh, my God!
- That's my idea of free
Ow. Ouch.
What happened to you?
It's a long story.
- I got shot.
- What?
And i-- i think
i'm wanted in Arizona.
Plus, my shoes
caught on fire.
You told me you were selling me
the top of the line.
The top of the line is digital.
Did you sell me a digital?
No, you did not.
So, i'm bringing it back,
and i expect a full refund.
And if you do not give me
a full refund, you will not...
be doing business
with myseIf or my company.
Thank you.
- So, did you hear?
- What?
Some, uh, vandaIs
broke in over the weekend.
- What?
- Well, nothing was stolen.
They-- They cut the--
the thingy...
off P.B.'s statue.
Um, they're reviewing
the videotape.
- Hi, everybody. How's it going?
- Not now, Nick.
- Did anybody see that game last night?
- Game? What game?
- Oh, that game. Overtime.
- Will you please shut up!
Don't touch it. Don't touch it.
Oh, you pig. Oh, you pig.
Well, that's it.
What's done is done. Listen.
I've got this great idea for
the new McGinty Cracker mascot.
- Move! Move! Move! Move! Move!
Thank you.
- This mascot--
- This--
- Nick! Shut up!
What's happening?
Well, what is this?
What the hell is this?
- I don't know.
- You goin' crazy as a spider!
Somebody must've recorded
over the tape.
- Who had access?
- Uh, there was an electrician
in here this morning.
What electrician?
I did not order an electrician!
I did. The flickers on the--
Fluorescent lights were flickering.
- I'm really sorry, sir.
- This is terrible, Phil.
- I would really like to be alone now.
- I'll go now.
- You should go.
- I would be really like to be alone.
- I'll leave now.
- You should go too.
- I would like to be
extremely alone for a minute.
- I'm gonna leave you alone.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Nick.
All right now. Cut that out.
Y'ali wanna eat? You wanna eat?
- Yeah, we wanna eat.
- I thought you wanna eat.
You wanna eat? All right.
- Just don't burn the meat.
- I don't never burn the meat.
- Uh-huh. What happened the last time?
- Hey, Dad don't burn the meat.
- i'm gonna put some more
po-po sauce on it. Y'ali like that.
- Joey. Tonya.
- Yeah, that's--
- Go see your mama, boy. You know.
Now this is my very
special mustard.
- Don't let nobody touch that.
- Okay, Mama.
- All right.
- Yeah.
So, how's the
electrician business?
Hey. Not bad.
The hours are a bitch.
i wanna thank you.
I don't know why-- I just wanna say
I appreciate what you did.
Well, don't mention it. How's that?
How did you know where I was anyway?
A friend gave me a tip.
A friend, huh?
- You hungry?
- Yes, we would love for you to join us.
Wouldn't we, Mama?
I talked to my boss today
after things settled down.
Convinced him we need
a new security system. Got any ideas?
Sure. I can help you
pick one out.
You wanna run it?
We need someone trustworthy.
I told him i know
just the guy.
Well, i'm gonna have to
think about this, Nick.
Right now, i'm weighing out
several lucrative offers.
I mean, they rollin' in.
A lot of people want me
to work for them right now.
Now, that's just
the way i like it.
All i need now is some
of Mama's special mustard.
Stop.
What'd i do?
- Run, run!
- Stay down, Nick. Get on outta here.
I'll beat you into the--
See you when you get there
Now i seen places and faces of things
you ain't never thought about thinkin'
If you ain't peeked then you
must be drinkin' and smokin'
Pretendin' that you're locin'
but you're broken, let me get you open
Now, little Timmy got his diploma
and little Jimmy got life
And Tamica around the corner
just took her first hit off the pipe
The other homey shot the other homey
and ran off with his money
And when the other homeys heard about it
they thought that it was funny
But who's the dummy 'cause now
you done lost a hustler
A down-ass brother
done replaced by a bustler
And though I got love for ya
i know I can't trust ya
'Cause my crew is rollin' numbers
and your crew is rollin' dusters
And just because of that you act
like you don't like a brother no more
I guess that's just
the way you go
I ain't tryin' to preach, i believe
I can reach but your mind ain't prepared
I see ya when you get there
I'll see you
when you get there
If you ever get there
See you when you get there
I'll see you
when you get there
If you ever get there
See you when you get there
More temptation and fate
I guess we livin' for today
I seen a man get swept off his feet
by a bull with an AK
The situation's so twisted
everybody gettin' lifted
i'm just tryin' to take care
of my kids and handle my business
'Cause it's way too serious
so you gotta pay close attention
So you don't get caught slippin'
when they come to do all the gettin'
Life is a big game so you gotta
play it with the big boys
Some of us gotta run a little faster
'cause we gotta lay the straw
But i'd be a fool to surrender
when i know i can be a contender
If everybody's ascended
then everybody can be a winner
No matter your rag color
Deep down we all brothers
And we gonna set a time
Somebody up there still love us
i'm gonna scuffle and struggle with ya
i'm breathless and weak
I done strived my whole life
to make it to the mountain peak
Always keep reachin'
Sure to grab onto somethin'
I'll be there when you get there
waitin' with the sounds bumpin'
I'll see you
when you get there
If you ever get there
See you when you get there
I'll see you
when you get there
If you ever get there
See you when
you get there
As we walk down the road
of our destiny
And the time comes to choose
which shall it be
The wide and crooked
or the straight and narrow
We got one voice to give
and one life to live
Stand up for somethin'
or lay down in the game
Listen to the song
that we sing
It's up to you
to make your beef
I guess i'll see you
when you see me
I'll see you
When you get there
If you wanna get there
- I'll see you
- When you get there
- If you wanna get there
- If you really
- I'll see you
- When you get there
- If you wanna get there
- If you really
I'll see you
When you get there